take a look at my hand i've got a green
and a purple belt on my hand from last
episode and i've even added it to the
brand new front that i have constructed
on my base so i'm adding all the
different colors and i'm about to go and
see if i can grab myself a new color for
my collection
oh my goodness there's some there's some
builds going on in the background stress
is creating some kind of
a pink cake factory or
is it a mushroom oh we got it we got to
check this out we haven't really checked
up on what stress is doing over here
it's like a it's like a fairy tale
factory i don't know i'm not sure what
it is i think it's a mushroom it looks
pretty cool though good job stress
anyway let's not get distracted we need
to go and check what's going on in the
button also i've i've never ever
questioned why my portal is on top of
this tree it just it just sort of sprung
here when everything moved to the top of
the nether and i just never questioned
it let's go and check what's going on
with the button but we have to be
careful because uh i think people might
be stalking it at this very moment yeah
there's someone there i'm not sure who
it is that says doc m77 oh there's
someone else there oh goodness it must
be it must be pretty uh good color to be
honest if it's uh if there's people
stalking it oh my goodness there's so
many people here what's going on all
right we need to know what color this is
so we're gonna go up high we're gonna
fly because in the nether there's
actually quite a lot of uh fog in fact
there's so much i can't actually see
where the button is and it looks like
it's a green it's a green belt we've
already got a green color so i guess we
just need to abide our time until that's
yellow it looks like everyone's trying
to get a yellow belt at this point part
of me just wants to press the button at
green
i don't know why i just i just kind of
want to spoil this this standoff that's
going on oh someone pressed it
someone
[Laughter]
someone invisible got away with it i
don't know who it was
i think i think that might have been
scar
greed for life
okay so we didn't manage to collect a
new stone but we still got far we got a
lot of actually how many colors have we
got left to get so we currently have a
purple belt and a green belt that means
we need
blue
yellow orange and red ah that's going to
be tough but blue's the easiest one to
get it's going to be many hours before
we get some of the the better stones i
mean belts well now that the button has
been reset
there's something that i've had in mind
to make some very good diamonds so as
you know my base is coming along quite
nicely and my stockpile of diamonds is
not i've got 53 but i can definitely do
with some more now i've had this idea i
had a quick look at some of the hermit's
bases one of them is iscao's omega giant
tree of
fun and happiness no not doing fun and
happiness
and i couldn't help but notice
he's gonna have a really rough time i
just used my rockets i'm gonna slowly
fall down while i talk about this
he's going to need a lot of leaves to
make this work and collecting leaves is
not particularly fun yeah there's
nothing i could do about this falling
so what i've decided to do
is a custom shop the hms ggg is going to
deliver goodies that they need
specifically for their mega bases and
hopefully we can make a quick bit of
diamonds when we do it ah now i've got a
i can't believe i got it i gotta walk i
gotta walk all the way back now cause
i'm out of rockets
emergency rockets i always keep
emergency rockets
i think this guy's actually in in here
oh yeah he's here yeah yeah i'm just
just you know pop popping in just
popping just popping in
you imagine just agree and popping
through your wall he has no idea by the
way what i have planned so hopefully
he's got some diamonds saved
because this is gonna be quite the
project what we're gonna do is head over
to a forest far far away we're gonna
grab our shears and some spares and some
boxes and we are going to harvest as
many leaves as possible
let's go
[Music]
as a nature lover this really hurts my
soul this was about three hours of
grinding i managed to watch an entire
movie while doing this
and it kind of hurts i mean i know it's
just a video game but
i don't like her in the trees like this
i really don't and i thought it would be
funny to leave all of the logs here just
to show the scale of this but check it
out there are lots and lots and lots and
lots and lots and lots of leaves here
and we will sell them all to iskall at a
mega discount so let's take all of these
and go and produce the hms ggg in the
air or maybe it should be called the hms
pesky bird i've successfully moved all
of the leaves over here and there is
quite a lot but since it's been
about three hours since i checked the
button before we go over to make
iskall's private personal
customized shop for all these leaves i
want to go check on the button again see
what's occurring we als we remember we
need to collect all of them and it might
be that it's on blue or maybe even
yellow we might as well take the
opportunity oh
excuse me
what is going on here there is this is
such a mess oh my goodness this is
totally unacceptable
what a mess
what have you been doing what on earth
this is uh i i have a skin just for this
occasion i have like i have about 30 odd
skins that if i need them they're there
and it's about time i got to use this
one let me put it on boom janet's
agreeing ready to clean up let's just uh
let's just clean this up this is just
this is just no this is just not good
this is not good
unacceptable
totally unacceptable wait we didn't even
check what it was on oh it's on blue
it's on blue play it cool play it cool
play it cool
ah look at all this mess
i don't i don't think i'm on board with
this this is this is so
this is so messy what's going on here
this is uh
no i i'm genuine about this janitor
thing i think i don't think we should
make this mess i like the button the way
it is mumbo's made a beautiful build and
everyone's desecrating it no no no no no
no roller coaster no no no mess mess
mess mess mess
gotta tidy all this up sweep sweep sweep
sweep sweep i i can i can stand the
chair you should you should all be a you
should all be ashamed
ashamed of the mess
what a mess and now
i'll press the button run
run
gotta scoop that up bye-bye
[Laughter]
lulled them into a full sense of
security
got him and now i can add the blue
concrete
makes a fine addition to my collection
and i've also added it to my hand on the
right as you can see now these are the
easiest colors to get in this game so
all the others they may take some time
i'm gonna have to really keep an eye out
now it's time to go build that shop for
iskall now that we're all prepared and
i've even found this little guy aka
pesky bird
so this little guy is gonna help keep
our shop in the air now for that i'm
gonna have to rename him and one of the
best things about using anvils all over
your base
is that you can use them at any time
pesky bird there we go boom
pesky bird no don't leave now i need you
come back where'd you go
oh yeah
forgot about that okay so i'm just gonna
pop you there for now we're gonna need
you a little later on i've got all the
resources that i think i'm going to need
for this and off we go oh man the lag on
the server look nothing's loading you
know when i get all of these infinity
stones oh sorry
infinity belts i am definitely
i am definitely definitely going to snap
the lag out of this server 50 off on the
lag
all right let's take a look let's see if
his skull is here
doesn't look
like it i've never actually been inside
here oh he started decorating well he's
been busy now we want to place this shot
just
about i would say about here yeah we
want it we want it quite far up
so that he's gonna see it up we go now
this is gonna be modeled after the uh
hms ggg mark one so we're gonna need
lots of campfires
i'm playing a dangerous game with him
being afk i probably should have waited
for him to just be entirely off the
server what i like about this is it's
actually not too difficult to make now
how many we're gonna need quite a a lot
of chests actually now that i think
about it we're gonna need
a lot of chests going on here to make to
make this work now we want our pesky
bird to be all the way up here connect
them all up with some fences
uh-oh
he's uh
he's back
unfortunately it doesn't look like he's
here he might be at his other base but i
need to i need to speed things up really
really fast
right come on pesky bird you're coming
with me
now to get the
to get this guy to follow me i can't fly
away really fast i kind of have to
wander and let him teleport to me come
on there he goes
from a distance it's gonna look like
it's floating but as soon as you get
close you'll see that pesky bird here is
looking after it let's see if he will go
on this
come on come on pesky bird there he is
right now we have to push him
right in the middle
and then if we remove this there we go
pesky bird he's he is completely
carrying the shop that's awesome okay if
i do single chests not only does it look
like more i'll i'll be able to count
exactly how many leaves i am giving
iskall
giving or selling sorry selling i'm not
i'm not i'm not doing this i'm not doing
this out of the the kindness of my heart
no no no no
okay now we got to transport all of the
leaves over here which is going to take
a long time
and still no sign of iscal so all going
well so far
i think i've been fairly lucky he must
be working on something else at the
moment
so each chest has 27 slots so that's 27
stacks
once we know exactly how many leaves we
have to sell him
then we can work out exactly how much
we're going to charge because that's the
next question i have no idea how much to
actually charge your scale for this and
by the way he gets the whole thing he he
can do the tidying up afterwards as well
he gets all the chests he gets all of
the campfires everything the whole barge
maybe not the pesky bird might have to
ask for him back i'm pretty sure he only
wants the oak leaf so that's what we're
gonna put in there this is true
door-to-door salesman tactics here there
are 11 full chests and then there's this
one which has half so 20
let me get the calculator out
okay so there is 297
stacks
of leaves in here plus
plus 14 in there so there is a total of
311.
now if i want to i need to work out what
to charge for this now now if i do six
stacks for one diamond now that's a
pretty good deal if you ask me
a really really good deal in fact i
might make it just around 60. 60
diamonds for all of these leaves welcome
to the hms pesky bird flying to give you
a great deal
today's offer is the entire barge for
just 60 diamonds
you get all of it minus the pesky bird
and there is
311 stacks of leaves now if that is not
a deal that entices our first targeted
customer then i don't know what i think
that is a genuinely a phenomenal deal
but there's actually there's one thing
that has to be done before we can call
this complete
and i'm sure i can find a block of it
somewhere
naha
one of these
directly underneath pesky bird
boop
you get a get a nice dollop of bird poop
with every transaction you're just
adding to the value pesky bird
okay and i think
i think we're done i think we are done
here
so the real question now is if he does
take this deal from the pesky bird who's
next
who is next who needs a lot and i mean a
lot of a specific block that takes a
while to get who can we give an offer
that is difficult to refuse especially
from such a handsome little bird as you
pb
all right let's go back to our base now
and hope that iskall sees that
and uh yeah i hope they accept the offer
might as well do a quick button check
oh
we are approaching yellow
that is very tempting we got to keep an
eye on that and it doesn't look like
anyone's around to to snipe it from us
either
let's just uh keep uh keep an eye on
that one
now that that's out of the way i feel
like we could do another quick building
of the base a little time lapse perhaps
we can tackle some of these areas over
here maybe some detailing and maybe even
what i wanted to do over here so let's
give that a crack and start some time
lapse
[Music]
you know what that was actually a really
really good time lapse
i think this edition although it's very
very tall it looks cool i think it
actually
really sets everything in and then scar
helped me out with a little bit of
terraining here he's such a good guy
and i think that all of that has come
together really nicely i added a few
details as i said um i think they look
okay and then i stopped when i got to
this bit because the difference is
that's a flat surface this is a one
block diagonal which is a lot easier to
detail than a two block diagonal i'll
get to this bit but i just need a little
time to work it all out because when i
work out that bit detailing this will
also become a lot easier like i've said
many times already this base is going to
be a very very long term project this is
not a build that will spring up
overnight you know that time lapse was
several hours of work and what do we
have to show for it couple of windows
bit of terrain and part of a tower it's
going to be a really long time before
this is finished
but i'm just i'm enjoying it and i think
it's coming out really nice once that's
mirrored on the other side
man it's uh it's getting bigger and
bigger remember it was just a platform
then it was this bit and now it's got
this bit down the bottom and on the
sides i don't know it just i don't know
it looks awesome but since it has been a
little while let's go and check on the
pesky bird i did actually add a bunch of
diorite here one two three as if as if
the pesky bird is continuing to poop
all over this thing now this here these
blocks this causes a bit of a dilemma
for iskall because of course the signs
here say you get
everything the entire barge now that
means not only to us okay so he hasn't
bought it but not only does he get the
leaves
but he has to at the same time purchase
this block
and he hates
diorite he hates it with a burning
passion so the longer he takes the more
pesky bird is going to release his um
yeah
so hopefully a skull gets a move on and
buys that and then we can move the pesky
bird
somewhere else and get some more
diamonds from people
it might be worth a quick check on the
button to see where we're at
we still have three
and
oh
we're over the halfway point that's very
close to yellow
it might be worth sitting here for a
while and waiting just for that to tick
down because it can't be too long you
know i literally wasn't here that long
and it's gone down to yellow i
do i just take it as it is there's
there's not really anyone online but i
don't know if i want to take the risk i
could theory in theory wait a little bit
longer but i think these are like hours
and hours you know i can't i i'm an
impatient man
[Music]
yay
a fine addition to my collection nice we
have we have
four four colors now admittedly still
the easiest only two more before we
bring balance to the server we'll add
this
onto the top
nice
looking good looking good hello hello
hello
hello hello i gotta keep up my trading
hall here
i i turned off this resource pack a few
times just because
as funny as it is
it does get old it does get old but i
i'll try my best to keep it on because i
know that a lot of you really love it i
got over it i love it too
in small doses in small doses uh ren
says i'm in need of industrial amounts
of tnt deals are welcome
well that looks like a job for the old
pesky bird if you ask me
let's go and check what our stocks are
like oh it's looking a bit yes it's not
looking too happy and i think
this is like the equivalent of finding
lint in your pockets when you're asked
for money uh i think it might be time to
run this machine for a bit let me just
tnt or gunpowder because you know tnt is
uh it's a lot of sand
a lot of sand right let's turn the
creeper farm on get it going
gunpowder preferably gotta watch my bank
account
okay
we could do this okay so i think that's
actually a really good place to end this
episode i'm gonna be running this
creeper farm for a little while and we
will get the next pesky bird delivery
sorted out for rendog lots and lots of
gunpowder but here's the thing just like
the diorite on iskall's delivery every
single pesky bird delivery service is
gonna have
some kind of catch that they won't know
about i mean it wouldn't be called a
pesky bird delivery without a little bit
of pesky if you know what i mean so
that's it for today's episode thank you
very much for watching of course and
good
bye don't tell ren